If you're not willing to hold the
candidates that you want to win
to any standard of ethics
then I don't know what you think they're
going to do when they win.
Because you've already shown them
that they can just
do the opposite
of what you have demanded of them
and still get your support.
Now, for the record, y'all know I don't
even believe in electoral politics.
What I do believe in is the people.
And it is quite disheartening
to watch people who I know are smart who
who I know are principled
continuously fall prey
to establishment politics
instead of demanding
that the folks that they support
be deeply
and solidly
against capitulating to it.
>> Get your energy right. Come and join me,
Amanda Seales, this Wednesday, August
12th, and every second Wednesday at
Comedy in Harlem for Radical Rhythms
experience. Every month we come together
to level up our vibration with music,
humor, and each other. Tickets available
at comedyinharlem.com.